oftentimes when I make new patterns for my EBF and vacuum freezers
I get asked why do I make patterns with the hot ingots
now I know how much some of you love ore-dictionary card
and what I'm going to say works different in different mod packs
the thing is that I don't see any real advantage in making edited patterns that don't show the hot ingots
like, yeah
you have one less pattern to deal with
but the one you have to make is a little bit more complicated
so my take is that most people do that
only because they feel better if they use the ore-dictionary card
but if you pattern hot ingots there are some advantages
the biggest one is that most of the times you're waiting for EBF while the vacuum freezer has nothing to do
but sometimes when you do some specific ingot
EBF will be faster than the vacuum freezer
and your vacuum freezer will be stuck cooling things
if you pattern hot ingots
you can make a dedicated interface with blocking mode for those ingots
that way, the ingots that are faster to cool than to melt can pass
in front of those slower ingots
and you can keep working on other things while your superconductor slowly cool down
another advantage is that you can see from AE2 crafting UI what the issue is
here we can guess ingots are waiting to be inserted into the vacuum freezer
here we can see a lot of ingots queued up inside the vacuum freezer that are being cooled down
while here the issue is the EBF having trouble blasting some tough materials
as you normally expect
another reason which I'm not vouching for too much
is that you can also fine tune how many ingots are going inside the machines at once
to better use the parallel capacity of each machine
another reason is that, in GTNH end game mostly
you will probably want to use crafting input buffers and crafting input proxies
and unless you want to optionally filter the output of a Gorge
you most likely want to either redo all of the patterns once you get those
or if you do hot ingots patterns early on
you already have the patterns done
now those were my takes mostly for GTNH
maybe I forgot something
maybe it's different in other packs
I don't know
I just wanted to put that in a video
so every time someone asks me
I can point them to this video
bye bye
通常当我为我的EBF和真空冷冻机制作新样板时
有人问我为什么要把热锭写在样板里
现在我知道你们中的一些人很爱用矿物词典卡
接下来我要说的观点，不一定在别的包里适用
我认为问题是，我不知道不用热锭的样板有什么真正优点
也就是说
你少了一个要写的样板
但是你要写的那个样板就比较复杂
我的看法是，大多数人这样做
那是因为他们用矿物词典卡感觉舒服一些
但是你在样板中写热锭的话，有一些实实在在的好处
最大的好处是，大多数时候你都在等待EBF，而真空冷冻机无事可做
但有时，你做某些锭时
EBF会比真空冷冻机快
你的真空冷冻机会卡在冷却东西上
如果你把热锭写在样板里
您可以为这些热锭制作具有阻挡模式的专用接口
这样，冷却速度快于烧制速度的钢锭就可以进入
排在那些冷的慢的锭面前
当你在等超导体慢慢冷却下来时，你可以继续做其他事情
另一个优点是，你可以从AE2制作界面上看到
这个时候，我们可以猜到锭正在等待放入真空冷冻机
这个时候，我们可以看到许多钢锭在真空冷冻机内排队冷却
而这个时候，EBF在烧难烧的材料时遇到了麻烦
就像你想的那样
另一个我非常支持的点是
你还可以微调一次进入机器的锭的数量
更好地利用每台机器的并行容量
另一个原因是，在GTNH的后期，大多数时候
你可能会使用样板输入总成和镜像
除非你想选择性地过滤神锻的输出
一旦你得到这些，你很可能想重新编辑所有的样板
或者如果你之前就做了热锭的样板
你就不需要再写一次样板
这些是我在GTNH包里的看法
也许我有什么没想到的地方
也许其他包里不一样
我不知道
我只是想把我的看法做成一个视频
每当有人问我这个问题
我就可以给他们看这个视频
拜拜